RoomID—-PuzzleID—-Riddle—-Choice—-Solution—-Hint
E6--P1--Sticks and stones me break me, but exercise will ache me.--Woods, Body, Bones, Heart--Bones--Can be brittle as I grow old.
W7--P2--Without me you cannot survive but fill a room with me and you would surely die.--Love, Sunlight, Money, Water--Water--Feels good to the body.
F5--P3--Born through fire, I'm lost in winds and muddied in water.--Soot, Ash, Smoke, Ember--Ash--I’m the last one left.
M7--P4--What is black when you acquire it, red when you use it, and grey when you dispose of it?"--Coal, Iron, Ashes, Anvil--Coal--I’m found beneath your feet.
D6--P5--Some live in me, some live on, and some shave me to stride upon. I rarely leave my native land. Until my death I always stand. High and low I may be found. Both above and underground.--Tree, Mountain, House--Tree--Every year, gifts are placed beneath me.
D2--P6--I am mother and father, but never birth. I'm rarely still, but I never wander.--Earth, Time, Nature--Earth--I can get real hot.
M3--P7--I can get you almost anything you want, but with no one to accept me, I am worthless.--Revenge, Power, Money--Money--People will fight over me.